Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Social Sciences Resource Center, Symposia
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Libraries, Social Sciences Resource Center, symposia [videorecordings]
2003-2006
V0323
Stanford University. Libraries. Social Sciences Resource Center
2 Linear feet
Videorecordings (primarily Beta and digital cassette formats) of the following symposia: War and Peace Symposium, 2003; Politics and the Press: Who Has the Power?, 2004; Intellectual Property in the Digital Age: The Tragedy of the Commons Revisited, 2005; and Trade Liberalization and Its Consequences, 2006. Presenters in 2004 included Shanto Iyengar, James Bettinger, and Jon Krosnick; from 2005, Glenn Otis Brown, Pamela Davis Kivelson, and Lauren K. Schoenthaler; and from 2006, Supacahai Panitchpakdi, John Taylor, and Santiago Levy.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
Access: viewing copies will need to be made prior to patron use.
Description of the Collection
Videorecordings (primarily Beta and digital cassette formats) of the following symposia: War and Peace Symposium, 2003; Politics and the Press: Who Has the Power?, 2004; Intellectual Property in the Digital Age: The Tragedy of the Commons Revisited, 2005; and Trade Liberalization and Its Consequences, 2006. Presenters in 2004 included Shanto Iyengar, James Bettinger, and Jon Krosnick; from 2005, Glenn Otis Brown, Pamela Davis Kivelson, and Lauren K. Schoenthaler; and from 2006, Supacahai Panitchpakdi, John Taylor, and Santiago Levy.
Access Terms
Bettinger, James.; Bettinger, James.; Brown, Glenn Otis.; Brown, Glenn Otis.; Iyengar, Shanto.; Iyengar, Shanto.; Kivelson, Pamela Davis.; Kivelson, Pamela Davis.; Krosnick, Jon A.; Krosnick, Jon A.; Santiago, Levy.; Santiago, Levy.; Schoenthaler, Lauren K.; Schoenthaler, Lauren K.; Stanford University. Libraries. Social Sciences Resource Center; Supachai Panitchpakdi.; Supachai Panitchpakdi.; Free trade.; Intellectual property.; Press and politics--United States.
Collection Contents
- Videorecordings
  - War and Peace Symposium, camera 1, tape 1 of 2, May 22, 2003, Betacam (Box 1)
  - War and Peace Symposium, camera 1, tape 2 of 2, May 22, 2003, Betacam (Box 1)
  - War and Peace Symposium, camera 2, tape 1 of 2, May 22, 2003, Betacam (Box 1)
  - War and Peace Symposium, camera 2, tape 2 of 2, May 22, 2003, Betacam (Box 1)
  - Politics and the press: Who has the power? [final] May 10, 2004, Betacam (Box 1)
  - Politics and the press, May 20, 2004, DVcam (Box 1)
  - Politics and the press, camera 1, tape 1, May 10, 2004, Betacam (Box 2)
  - Politics and the press, camera 1, tape 2, May 10, 2004, Betacam (Box 2)
  - Politics and the press, camera 2, tape 1, May 10, 2004, Betacam (Box 2)
  - Politics and the press, camera 2, tape 2, May 10, 2004, Betacam (Box 2)
  - Politics and the press: Who has the power? [final] May 10, 2004, VHS (Box 2)
  - Intellectual property in the digital age: the tragedy of the commons revisited [final] tape 1 of 2, April 27, 2005, Betacam (Box 3)
  - Intellectual property in the digital age: the tragedy of the commons revisited [final] tape 2 of 2, April 27, 2005, Betacam (Box 3)
  - Intellectual property in the digital age: the tragedy of the commons revisited; camera 1, tape 1 of 2, Betacam (Box 3)
  - Intellectual property in the digital age: the tragedy of the commons revisited; camera 1, tape 2 of 2, Betacam (Box 3)
  - Intellectual property in the digital age: the tragedy of the commons revisited; camera 2, tape 1 of 2, Betacam (Box 3)
  - Intellectual property in the digital age: the tragedy of the commons revisited; camera 2, tape 2 of 2, Betacam (Box 3)
  - Trade Conference, London Economics Bldg., welcome/keynote, tape 1, April 27, 2006, DVcam (Box 4)
  - Trade Conference, London Economics Bldg., session I, tape 2, April 27, 2006, DVcam (Box 4)
  - Trade Conference, London Economics Bldg., session II, tape 3, April 27, 2006, DVcam (Box 4)
  - Trade Conference, London Economics Bldg., session III & IV, tape 4, April 27, 2006, DVcam (Box 4)
  - Trade Conference, London Economics Bldg., Keynote, Session V, tape 5, April 27, 2006, DVcam (Box 4)
  - Trade Conference, London Economics Bldg., session VI, tape 6, April 28, 2006, DVcam (Box 4)
  - Trade Conference, SSRC, Graphics session 6 tape 6, April 28, 2006, DVcam (Box 4)
  - Trade Conference, London Economics Bldg., tape 1, April 28, 2006, DVcam (Box 4)
  - Trade conference, camera 1 (tape 1 and 2), 4/26/06, MiniDV (Box 4)
  - Trade conference, camera 2 (tape 1 and 2), 4/26/06, MiniDV (Box 4)
  - Trade conference, (tape 1 through 7), 4/27/05-4/28/06, MiniDV (Box 4)
  - Trade conference, (tape 1, 2, 3 – copies for Ron?) 4/27/06, MiniDV (Box 4)
  - Trade conference, SSRC, Session 6, camera 1, (tapes 1-4 of 4), 4/28/06, MiniDV (Box 4)
  - Trade conference, SSRC, Session 6, camera 2, (tapes 1-3 of 3), 4/28/06, MiniDV (Box 4)